vietmusic.net 2001-06-14

# Vietmusic Network Privacy Policy

Vietmusic is committed to protecting your privacy online. We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can on our Web site. In order to enhance your experience at our site we gather certain personal information about you that helps us customize our content to your tastes and preferences. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Website. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

What information do we collect?  
What information do parties other than Vietmusic collect?  
What are "cookies" and how do we use them?  
What do we do with the information we collect?  
With whom do we share your information and for what purpose?  
Your Consent  
Changes to our privacy policy

**What information do we Collect?**  
In our pageant, we collect your E-mail addresses and some of your personal information such as where you live and what is your favorite food or hobbies and so on...Though those are not specific information, your pictures are submitted to us and they may be reused or abused by net surfers.

In addition to that, we also accept your E-mails and names through submitted info when you are suggesting a website at Vietmusic.

**What information do parties other than Vietmusic collect?**  
Some advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you when you access or utilize those links. Vietmusic does not control the collection or use of such information, and the practices of those advertisers and Web sites are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

**What are "cookies" and how do we use them?**  
Vietmusic uses "Cookies" to track and record your preferences and activity on our Web site. Cookies are small bits of data that are sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. Your cookie may be set at various times during your interaction with our Web site. It is updated from time to time as you access the many different portions of our Web site. Each time you access our site, our server may deliver certain customized information to you based on the data stored in your cookie. 

Some advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may also use their own cookies.

We also collect IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to our sponsors and advertisers.

**What do we do with the information we collect?**  
Vietmusic's primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our Web site. The information we collect (including information contained in your cookie) may be used to provide such capabilities as personalization services, interactive communications, online shopping, and  
personalized communication between you and the artists you prefer. We may also use the information to estimate the size of our audience and measure certain traffic patterns, to track the progress and number of entries in our promotions and contests, to track visits to and business conducted at our online store, to notify our visitors about updates to our Web site, to contact you for marketing purposes, to contact you on behalf of certain artists and other third parties and deliver targeted advertisements that may be of interest to you. We may occasionally contact you with information regarding special events at Vietmusic.

**With whom do we share your information and for what purpose?**  
Vietmusic does not trade, rent, or sell any of the information we collected with any other parties. However, when one or more of our business partners co-sponsor a service, promotion and/or contest, we may share some or all of the information collected in connection with such service, promotion or contest with the co-sponsor(s). If we intend to share such information, you will be notified prior to the collection of that information. If you do not want your information to be shared, you will be able to choose not to allow the transfer by not using or signing up for that particular service, promotion or contest.

**Your Consent**  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by Vietmusic as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
From time to time, we may change our Privacy Policy. We will post those changes on this page so that our customers will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we share the information with others.
